Finding Aid for H. Edmund Curch papers, 1884-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
H. Edmund Curch papers 1884-1964
Curch, H. Edmund, 1873-1962.
1 linear foot
85119 Aa 2
Disciples of Christ clergyman; ministerial papers.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Mr. and Mrs. Carl McAlvey (donor no. 6355 ) and came to the library in 1979.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
H. Edmund Curch was a Disciples of Christ clergyman. He served in various Michigan communities, including Trowbridge and Belding.
The H. Edmund Curch collection includes correspondence and other materials concerning pastorates in Trowbridge and Belding, Michigan. There are also papers relating to organizational work for the denomination, including establishing new congregations and arrangements for holding conventions and conferences. Also retained were related state and national denominational printed material. Some of the papers are of his wife, Nettie Curch.
Subjects:
Belding (Mich.).; Clergy--Michigan.; Disciples of Christ--Michigan.; Trowbridge (Mich.).
Contributors:
Curch, Nettie.
- Ministerial papers, 1884-1964
  - Correspondence, reports and related items
    - 1884-1885 and 1897-1905 (Box 1)
    - 1906-1910 (Box 1)
    - 1911-1919 (Box 1)
    - 1920-1962 (Box 1)
  - Publications of individual Disciples Congregations (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous programs, announcements for conventions and other meetings of Disciples in Michigan, 1895-1964 (Box 1)
  - Clippings re. Disciples of Christ in Michigan (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous items for Michigan Disciples, undated, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications from the national missions agencies of the Disciples of Christ (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Disciples of Christ denominational tracts and publications (Box 1)
  - Church and Sunday School materials from non-Disciples of Christ groups and agencies (Box 1)
  - Two monographs on the history of the Disciples of Christ in Canada (Box 1)